Hello.
こんにちは
I'm the best.
僕が最上だね
Am I the best?
僕が最上?
Yeah, I heard that you have a really cute girl.
うん、すごい可愛い子がいるって聞いてたんですよ
I'm an idol for some reason
なんかアイドルやってるんで
Sho?
しょ?
I haven't done much.
め っちゃやってない
Are you not doing it now?
今はやってない?
I'm not doing it now.
今はやってない
Are you just a normal student now?
今はじゃあ普通に学生かな?
I usually work at a company.
普通に会社にしてます
Are you working?
働いてるんですか?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
The idol has arrived.
アイドル来たぞ
Doesn't everyone want to talk?
みんな、会話したくてない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
I want to?
したい?
I want to go on a date.
デートしたいです
What are your plans?
予定は?
none.
なし
What?
なんだ?
What about with friends?
友達となんか?
Maybe it will.
たぶんそうなるかな
It's not a date.
デートじゃないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's the season when things get pretty tough.
結構人肌こしくなる季節だし
This person seems nice.
この人いいなみたいな
why?
なんで?
Will there be any encounters?
出会いとかない?
There are no encounters at all.
出会い全然ないですよ
workplace?
職場?
Are you older?
あんま年上とかは?
I'm not older at all.
年上も全然ありないけど
Work is work.
仕事は仕事で
I can't speak to you much.
あんまり声かけられない
That's right.
そうなんだ
Isn't it difficult for everyone to speak out?
みんな声かけづらいんじゃない?
Is it difficult to apply?
かけづらいんですかね
Do you understand?
分かる?
Because I can't talk to cute girls.
可愛い子には声かけられないから
I want someone who is easy to talk to.
声かけやすいタイプがいいから
Looks like it will be difficult to get through.
かけにくそう
Well, it's a bit high level.
ちょっとね、レベル高いから
But if I don't get someone to introduce me,
でもやっぱ人使いで紹介してもらわないと、
I can't speak.
話せない
This hand,
この手はね、
I'd like her to wear something frilly.
フ リフリのやつとか着てもらいたいな
It definitely suits you, style.
絶対似合うね、スタイル
It's the best.
ベストだね
Slowly behind too.
後ろもゆっくり
I can grow my hair long too
髪も結構伸ばせる
Na.
な
Did you understand?
分 かった?
Are you wearing them?
履いてる?
I'm wearing them.
履いてますよ
Are you wearing them?
履いてる?
Is it a tea bag?
ティーバッグなの?
You have a great butt.
すごいお尻をしてるね
Something about my appearance and that.
なんか、外見とかあれで
There must be some people who have attacked it quite a bit.
結構攻めた人がいるんじゃない?
Only behind.
後ろだけ
Only the back?
後ろだけ?
So what's going on before?
じゃあ、前はどうなってるの?
forward?
前?
Do it behind you too.
後ろにもやって
It's also a bit creepy.
ちょっと気悪いのもね
You look like you have hair.
髪毛しそうだな、お前
It's being processed properly.
ちゃんと処理してるんだね
I feel like this Irusukesuke is good.
このイルスケスケがいいなって感じ
Should I buy it at a Shimoge shop?
下毛屋さんで買おう?
I buy it at a Shimoge shop.
下毛屋さんで買ってます
That's fine...
結構じゃ、イケイケ...
It's not cool.
イケイケじゃない
I like the undercoat.
下毛が好きなんだよね
I think you'll be surprised.
びっくりしちゃうと思う
Are you blaming me?
責めてますか?
A lot of blaming
責めてると、だいぶ
It gives me a good feeling, but it's also incredibly sexy inside.
いい 感じでくれるのに、 すごい中はセクシーだから
It's starting to burn out, isn't it?
燃えてきちゃってるでしょ
This is sexy.
セクシーだね、これね
When I looked inside, it was crossed.
中に見たら、クロスしちゃってんじゃん
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいじゃん
It's turning into hair.
下 毛になってます
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
I could have opened it.
開けたかもしれない
I want to live here.
ここに住みたいもんね
See inside?
中見る?
It's already worn out, so there's no need to change.
もうくすけてるからさ、 変わんなくない?
It's not hidden.
隠れてないね
I can't make it.
作れてないね
I feel like I want to stand out, but I don't like it.
目立ちたがり嫌な感じなんだけど
hey.
ね
Scratches, etc.
こ すれたりとかさ、
When you were a student, didn't you put stickers on things?
学 生の時とかさ、 シール貼ったりとかしなかった?
Didn't you put a sticker on it?
シール貼ったりしなかった?
learning time
ラーニングの時
Or something.
とか
Underhair.
下 毛って
Are both easy to feel?
どちらも感じやすい?
Oho?
おほ?
It's like a snack.
つまみたい
Did you lose your hair?
脱毛したの?
I haven't lost my hair.
脱毛してないね
I would love to do it myself.
自分でぜひやりしてんだ
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりするの?
Are you talking like this?
こんな口ぷち言ってるの?
oh
お
This is the ceiling.
天 井これ
This is my ceiling.
自分のお天井だよこれ
I'm so happy, so happy.
すごい嬉しいね、嬉しい
That's right here, right?
ここに当たるでしょ?
That's you.
お前それ
Do you understand?
分かる?
Touch it directly.
直手触って
Remove the back.
裏外して
I left it behind.
裏外したし
He touches me while licking my inner neck.
内首舐めながら触ってくれる
Lick the bottom too.
下も舐めて
Chin Chin too.
チンチンも
Be intense.
激しくして